RG 002:004, General Assembly Papers
Connecticut State Library
- 1913-1971, 1984-045
  - 1983
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 1133)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 1134)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 1135)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 1136)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 1137)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Education (Box 1138)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House; Energy and Public Utilities (Box 1139)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment (Box 1140)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue, and Bond (Box 1141)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue, and Bond (Box 1142)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue, and Bond (Box 1143)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue, and Bond (Box 1144)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 1145)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy (Box 1146)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy (Box 1147)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy (Box 1148)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services (Box 1149)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance (Box 1150)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 1151)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 1152)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 1153)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 1154)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 1155)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development (Box 1156)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety (Box 1157)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, Senate, House (Box 1151)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, House; Special Session (Box 1159)
- 1984-1989, 1992-036
  - 1984
    - Appointments (Box 1)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 1)
    - Veto Session (Box 1)
    - Special Sessions (Box 1)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 2)
    - Resolutions (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 1-85 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 86-130 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 151-220 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 221-254 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 255-300 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts 301-335 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 336-370 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 371-405 (Box 10)
    - Public Acts, 406-435 (Box 11)
    - Public Acts, 436-469 (Box 12)
    - Public Acts, 470-510 (Box 13)
    - Public Acts, 511-530 (Box 14)
    - Public Acts, 531-546 (Box 15)
    - Special Acts, 1-45 (Box 16)
    - Special Acts, 46-76 (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate and House (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House; Banks (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Public Utilities; Finance, Revenue and Bonding, Senate (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Revenue and Bonding, Senate (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Election (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary, Senate and House (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House; Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development, Senate (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development, House; Public Health; Public Safety; Transportation (Box 26)
  - 1985
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 27)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 27)
    - Appointments (Box 28)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 28)
    - Resolutions (Box 28)
    - Special Session (Box 29)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreements (Box 29)
    - Public Acts, 1-74 (Box 30)
    - Public Acts, 75-149 (Box 31)
    - Public Acts, 150-200 (Box 32)
    - Public Acts, 201-254 (Box 33)
    - Public Acts, 255-304 (Box 34)
    - Public Acts, 305-354 (Box 35)
    - Public Acts, 355-389 (Box 36)
    - Public Acts, 390-430 (Box 37)
    - Public Acts, 431-480 (Box 38)
    - Public Acts, 481-508 (Box 39)
    - Public Acts, 509-535 (Box 40)
    - Public Acts, 536-565 (Box 41)
    - Public Acts, 566-590 (Box 42)
    - Public Acts, 591-612 (Box 43)
    - Public Act 613 (Box 44)
    - Special Session - Public Act 1 (Box 44)
    - Special Acts, 1-66 (Box 45)
    - Special Acts, 57-112 (Box 46)
    - 1985 Reconvened Session - Adopted Resolutions (Box 46)
    - Special Session, July (Box 46)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate and House (Box 47)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House; Banks (Box 48)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House; Banks; Education, Senate and House (Box 49)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House; Energy and Public Utilities; Environment, Senate and House (Box 50)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment, House; Finance, Revenue and Bonding, Senate (Box 51)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, House (Box 52)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, House (Box 53)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 54)
    - Unfinished Business - General Administration and Elections; Human Services (Box 55)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 56)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 57)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 58)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 59)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees (Box 60)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 61)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety; Transportation (Box 62)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 63)
  - 1986
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 64)
    - Appointments (Box 64)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 65)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 65)
    - Resolutions (Box 65)
    - Special Session Resolutions (Box 65)
    - Collective Bargaining Contracts (Box 66)
    - Public Acts, 1-24 (Box 66)
    - Public Acts, 25-95 (Box 67)
    - Public Acts, 96-150 (Box 68)
    - Public Acts, 151-192 (Box 69)
    - Public Acts, 193-244 (Box 70)
    - Public Acts, 245-281 (Box 71)
    - Public Acts, 282-318 (Box 72)
    - Public Acts, 319-340 (Box 73)
    - Public Acts, 341-365 (Box 74)
    - Public Acts, 366-387 (Box 75)
    - Public Acts, 388-402 (Box 76)
    - Public Acts, 403-416 (Box 77)
    - Public Acts, 417-421 (Box 78)
    - Special Acts, 1-42 (Box 78)
    - Special Acts, 43-72 (Box 79)
    - Special Session, May - Public Act 1 and Special Act 1 (Box 79)
    - Special Session, June 11 - Public Act 1 (Box 79)
    - Special Session, June 23 - Public Act 1 and Special Act 1 (Box 79)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 80)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 81)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Educations; Energy and Public Utilities; Environment (Box 82)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 83)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; General Law (Box 84)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 85)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 86)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 87)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees, Legislative Management; Planning and Development; Public Health (Box 88)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 89)
  - 1987
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 90)
    - Appointments (Box 90)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Senate, Senate Joint, House, and House Joint) - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 90)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Senate, Senate Joint, House, and House Joint) - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 91)
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 91)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreements (Box 91)
    - Public Acts, 1-70 (Box 92)
    - Public Acts, 87-137 (Box 93)
    - Public Acts, 138-196 (Box 94)
    - Public Acts, 197-247 (Box 95)
    - Public Acts, 248-294 (Box 96)
    - Public Acts, 295-336 (Box 97)
    - Public Acts, 337-376 (Box 98)
    - Public Acts, 377-404 (Box 99)
    - Public Acts, 405-433 (Box 100)
    - Public Acts, 434-458 (Box 101)
    - Public Acts, 459-488 (Box 102)
    - Public Acts, 489-507 (Box 103)
    - Public Acts, 509-529 (Box 104)
    - Public Acts, 530-549 (Box 105)
    - Public Acts, 550-571 (Box 106)
    - Public Acts, 572-589 (Box 107)
    - Special Acts, 1-42 (Box 108)
    - Special Acts, 43-80 (Box 109)
    - Special Acts, 81-112 (Box 110)
    - Trailer Session (Box 110)
    - Special Session, Public Acts (Box 110)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 111)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate; Appropriations, House (Box 112)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 113)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 114)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, Senate; Education (Box 115)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House; Energy and Public Utilities; Environment, Senate (Box 116)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment, House; Family and the Workplace Select Committee; Finance, Revenue and Bonding, Senate (Box 117)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, Senate (Box 118)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, Senate; Finance, Revenue and Bonding, House (Box 119)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, House (Box 120)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, House; General Law; Government Administration and Elections, Senate; Government Administration and Elections, House (Box 121)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing Select Committee; Human Services, Senate; Human Services, House (Box 122)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services, House; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 123)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 124)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate; Judiciary, House (Box 125)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 126)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 127)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House; Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management (Box 128)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Program Review and Investigations (Box 129)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health (Box 130)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Substance Abuse Prevention; Transportation, Senate (Box 131)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, House (Box 132)
  - 1988
    - Appointments (Box 133)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 133)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 133)
    - Resolutions (Box 133)
    - Collective Bargaining Contracts (Box 134)
    - Collective Bargaining Contracts (Box 135)
    - Public Acts, 1-64 (Box 136)
    - Public Acts, 65-105 (Box 137)
    - Public Acts, 106-152 (Box 138)
    - Public Acts, 153-187 (Box 139)
    - Public Acts, 188-219 (Box 140)
    - Public Acts, 220-234 (Box 141)
    - Public Acts, 234-264 (Box 142)
    - Public Acts, 265-270 (Box 143)
    - Public Acts, 281-297 (Box 144)
    - Public Acts, 298-316 (Box 145)
    - Public Acts, 317-325 (Box 146)
    - Public Acts, 326-343 (Box 147)
    - Public Acts, 344-358 (Box 148)
    - Public Acts, 359-364 (Box 149)
    - Special Acts, 1-43 (Box 150)
    - Special Acts, 44-74 (Box 151)
    - Special Acts, 75-80 (Box 152)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate; Appropriations, House (Box 153)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 154)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Education; Energy and Public Utilities; Environment (Box 155)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Family and the Workplace; Finance, Revenue and Bonding, Senate (Box 156)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, House (Box 157)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, House; General Law; Government Administration and Elections, Senate (Box 158)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections, House; Housing; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 159)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 160)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 161)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Planning and Development (Box 162)
    - Unfinished Business - Program Review and Investigations; Public Health; Public Safety; Substance Abuse Prevention; Transportation (Box 163)
  - 1989
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 164)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Box 164)
    - Appointments (Box 164)
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 165)
    - Resolutions (Box 165)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreements (Box 165)
    - Public Acts, 1-21 (Box 165)
    - Public Acts, 22-91 (Box 166)
    - Public Acts, 92-147 (Box 167)
    - Public Acts, 148-194 (Box 168)
    - Public Acts, 195-226 (Box 169)
    - Public Acts, 227-250 (Box 170)
    - Public Acts, 251-260 (Box 171)
    - Public Acts, 261-295 (Box 172)
    - Public Acts, 296-324 (Box 173)
    - Public Acts, 325-350 (Box 174)
    - Public Acts, 351-368 (Box 175)
    - Public Acts, 369-383 (Box 176)
    - Public Acts, 384-390 (Box 177)
    - Special Acts, 1-37 (Box 178)
    - Special Acts, 38-58 (Box 179)
    - Trailer Session (Box 179)
    - Special Session (Box 179)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations Committee (Box 180)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations Committee (Box 181)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations Committee; Banks; Education (Box 182)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Public Utilities (Box 183)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Public Utilities; Environment (Box 184)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Family and Workplace; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 185)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 186)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 187)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 188)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 189)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Human Services (Box 190)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 191)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 192)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 193)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 194)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 195)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Health (Box 196)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety; Substance Abuse Prevention (Box 197)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 198)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 199)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreements (Box 199)
- 1990-1995, 1997-012
  - 1990
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 1)
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 1)
    - Appointments (Box 1)
    - Trailer Session (Box 1)
    - Special Session, June (Box 1)
    - Public Acts, 1-53 (Box 2)
    - Public Acts, 54-111 (Box 3)
    - Public Acts, 112-139 (Box 4)
    - Public Acts, 140-164 (Box 5)
    - Public Acts, 165-205 (Box 6)
    - Public Acts, 206-219 (Box 7)
    - Public Acts, 220-231 (Box 8)
    - Public Acts, 232-243 (Box 9)
    - Public Acts, 244-263 (Box 10)
    - Public Acts, 264-294 (Box 11)
    - Public Acts, 295-322 (Box 12)
    - Public Acts, 323-342 (Box 13)
    - Special Session, June 25 - Public Act 1 (Box 13)
    - Special Acts, 1-27 (Box 14)
    - Special Acts, 28-42 (Box 15)
    - Special Session, June 25 - Special Act 1 (Box 15)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 15)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 16)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 17)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Education; Energy and Public Utilities; Environment (Box 18)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Family and the Workplace; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 19)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 20)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 21)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 22)
    - Unfinished Business - Housing; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 23)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 24)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 25)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Health; Public Safety; Substance Abuse Prevention (Box 26)
    - Unfinished Business - Substance Abuse Prevention; Transportation; No Name Committee (Box 27)
  - 1991
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 28)
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 28)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Senate, Senate Joint, House, House Joint, Joint Conv.) - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 28)
    - Appointments (Box 28)
    - Public Acts, 1-31 (Box 29)
    - Public Acts, 32-59 (Box 30)
    - Public Acts, 60-120 (Box 31)
    - Public Acts, 121-168 (Box 32)
    - Public Acts, 169-201 (Box 33)
    - Public Acts, 202-236 (Box 34)
    - Public Acts, 238-258 (Box 35)
    - Public Acts, 259-285 (Box 36)
    - Public Acts, 286-304 (Box 37)
    - Public Acts, 305-325 (Box 38)
    - Public Acts, 326-340 (Box 39)
    - Public Acts, 341-359 (Box 40)
    - Public Acts, 360-382 (Box 41)
    - Public Acts, 383-400 (Box 42)
    - Public Acts, 401-409 (Box 43)
    - Special Acts, 1-41 (Box 44)
    - Special Acts, 42-44 (Box 45)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 45)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 46)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 47)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banks; Commerce; Education (Box 48)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Energy and Public Utilities (Box 49)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 50)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 51)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 52)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 53)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding; General Law (Box 54)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 55)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections; Housing (Box 56)
    - Unfinished Business - Housing; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 57)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 58)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 59)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor and Public Employees (Box 60)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 61)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Public Health; Public Safety (Box 62)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety (Box 63)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 64)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; No Name Committee (Box 65)
    - Trailer Session (Box 65)
    - Special Session, June 5 - Constitutional Amendments; Resolutions; Rejected Bills (Box 65)
    - Special Session, June 12 - Resolutions (Box 65)
    - Special Session, June 26 - Resolutions (Box 65)
    - Special Session, June 5 - Public Acts, 1-2 (Box 66)
    - Special Session, June 5 - Public Acts, 3-8 (Box 67)
    - Special Session, June 5 - Public Acts, 9-14 (Box 68)
    - Special Session, June 5 - Special Acts, 1-7 (Box 69)
    - Special Session, June 12 - Public Act 1 (Box 69)
    - Special Session, June 26 - Public Act 1 (Box 69)
    - Special Session, June 5 - Unfinished Business, SB 2007-2008, HB 8001 (Box 70)
    - Special Session, June 5 - Unfinished Business, HB 8002-8011 (Box 71)
    - Special Session, November 18 - Resolutions; Public Acts, 1-5; Unfinished Business, SB 4222-4225 (Box 72)
    - Special Session, November 18 - Unfinished Business, SB 4228, HB 9001-9011 (Box 73)
  - 1992
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 74)
    - Adopted Resolutions (Senate, Senate Joint, House, House Joint, Joint Conv.) - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 74)
    - Appointments (Box 74)
    - Public Acts, 1-33 (Box 75)
    - Public Acts, 34-77 (Box 76)
    - Public Acts, 78-93 (Box 77)
    - Public Acts, 94-126 (Box 78)
    - Public Acts, 127-157 (Box 79)
    - Public Acts, 158-177 (Box 80)
    - Public Acts, 178-210 (Box 81)
    - Public Acts, 211-236 (Box 82)
    - Public Acts, 237-261 (Box 83)
    - Public Acts, 262 (Box 84)
    - Special Acts, 1-13 (Box 84)
    - Special Acts, 14-27 (Box 85)
    - Special Session, May 12 - Resolutions; Rejected Bills and Resolutions; Public Acts, 1-7 (Box 85)
    - Special Session, May 12- Public Acts, 8-17 (Box 86)
    - Special Session, May 12 - Special Acts, 1-3 (Box 87)
    - Special Session, June 22 - Resolutions; Rejected Bills and Resolutions; Public Act 1; Resolutions (Box 87)
    - Special Session, June 25 - Public Act 1 (Box 87)
    - Reconvened Session, July - Resolutions (Box 87)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 87)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 88)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Banks, Commerce, Education (Box 89)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Public Utilities; Environment (Box 90)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 91)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 92)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 93)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding (Box 94)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bonding, General Law; Government Administration and Elections (Box 95)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections (Box 96)
    - Unfinished Business - Housing, Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 97)
    - Unfinished Business - Judicial (Box 98)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 99)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development; Program Development and Review; Public Health; Public Safety (Box 100)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation (Box 101)
    - Unfinished Business - Special Session, May 12, No Committee Name (Box 101)
    - Unfinished Business - Special Session, June 22, Public Safety, Judiciary (Box 101)
  - 1993
    - Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 102)
    - Resolutions (Box 102)
    - Appointments (Box 102)
    - Appointments (Box 103)
    - Public Acts, 1-28 (Box 103)
    - Public Acts, 29-59 (Box 104)
    - Public Acts, 60-80 (Box 105)
    - Public Acts, 80-113 (Box 106)
    - Public Acts, 114-138 (Box 107)
    - Public Acts, 139-155 (Box 108)
    - Public Acts, 156-187 (Box 109)
    - Public Acts, 188-219 (Box 110)
    - Public Acts, 220-229 (Box 111)
    - Public Acts, 230-248 (Box 112)
    - Public Acts, 249-262 (Box 113)
    - Public Acts, 263-278 (Box 114)
    - Public Acts, 279-297 (Box 115)
    - Public Acts, 298-310 (Box 116)
    - Public Acts, 311-330 (Box 117)
    - Public Acts, 331-342 (Box 118)
    - Public Acts, 343-356 (Box 119)
    - Public Acts, 357-373 (Box 120)
    - Public Acts, 374-384 (Box 121)
    - Public Acts, 385-402 (Box 122)
    - Public Acts, 403-418 (Box 123)
    - Public Acts, 419-428 (Box 124)
    - Public Acts, 429-435 (Box 125)
    - Special Acts, 1-7 (Box 125)
    - Special Acts, 8-40 (Box 126)
    - Special Acts, 41-42 (Box 127)
    - Special Session, June 10 - Resolutions; Public Acts; Special Acts (Box 127)
    - Trailer Session, July 12 - Resolutions (Box 127)
    - Special Session, July 12 - Resolutions (Box 127)
    - Special Session, September 22 - Resolutions; Public Acts (Box 127)
    - Special Session, October 20 - Resolutions and Public Acts; Public Acts; Special Acts (Box 128)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 128)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 129)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 130)